all:
Aye, aye, Captain!
全部：
是啊是啊，队长！
- I can't hear you.
- 我听不到你说话。
all:
Aye, aye, Captain!
全部：
是啊是啊，队长！
- * Ohh... *
-*哦...*
* Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? *
*谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ *
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- * Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he *
- * 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的*
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- * If nautical nonsense
be something you wish *
- *如果航海废话
成为你所希望的*
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- * Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish *
- * 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通 *
all: SpongeBob SquarePants!
所有：海绵宝宝！
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
SpongeBob SquarePants!
- SpongeBob
- 海绵宝宝
SquarePants!
方裤！
* *
**
- Mm, ooh!
- 嗯，哦！
Order's up!
- Ahh!
订单到了！
- 啊！
Another pair of perfect patties.
另一对完美的肉饼。
Hand 'em over, Squidward.
- Wait!
把它们交出来，章鱼哥。
- 等待！
Tink.
叮当声。
Okay, now they're perfect.
好吧，现在他们就完美了。
- Ohh, aha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
- 哦，啊哈，哈，哈，哈，哈。
- Ooh! Ooh! Ooh! Ooh! Ooh!
- 哦！哦！哦！哦！哦！
- Ay, ay, ha, ha--okay. Enough.
- 哎，哎，哈，哈——好吧。足够的。
Everybody gets it.
Our patties are perfect.
每个人都明白。
我们的肉饼很完美。
Keep them orders coming,
boyos!
让他们接到订单，
男孩！
Doo, dee, doop, dee,
doop, doop, doop,
杜，迪，杜，迪，
杜普、杜普、杜普、
doo, dee, doop, doop, doo.
杜，迪，杜，杜，杜。
Orders up!
Two Krabby Patties.
订单上架！
两块蟹肉饼。
- Oh, uh, yeah.
I don't know.
- 哦，呃，是的。
我不知道。
- Something wrong with
the patties, sir
- 有问题
肉饼，先生
- No. We just want
something, like, different.
- 不，我们只是想要
一些不同的东西。
- Yeah. Something, like, new.
- 是的。一些新的东西。
both: New, new, new, new.
两者：新，新，新，新。
- Hey, we want something
new, too!
- 嘿，我们想要一些东西
也有新的！
all: New! New! New
全体：新！新的！新的
Oh.
哦。
New, huh? We've been waiting
to test our, uh,
新的吧？我们一直在等待
来测试我们的，呃，
our new menu!
我们的新菜单！
Uh, how'd you like to be
the first to try it?
呃，你想成为怎样的人
第一个尝试的？
- Yeah. We like being first.
- 是的。我们喜欢成为第一。
- Eeh!
- 呃！
- Come with me, boyo.
- 跟我来吧，男孩。
* *
**
- It's me secret lab
- 这是我的秘密实验室
where I experiment on food.
我在那里进行食物实验。
- Oh, Mr. Krabs,
this looks like madness.
-哦，蟹老板先生，
这看起来很疯狂。
Ooh, wait till you see...
哦哦，等你看到...
This!
- Yipe!
这！
- 伊佩！
- Howdy, SpongeBob.
- 你好，海绵宝宝。
What are you
doing down here?
你是什么
在这里做什么？
- I'm moonlighting as
a molecular gastronomist.
- 我兼职
分子美食家。
A maladowin
马拉多温
- Eugene here is paying me
to science up his menu.
- 尤金付钱给我
科学地完善他的菜单。
- Look, I'm in a hurry.
- 听着，我很着急。
You have this special project.
你有这个特殊的项目。
- Well, it's a work in progress.
- 嗯，这是一项正在进行的工作。
Huh.
- Hm.
呵呵。
- 嗯。
- There it is.
Your new patty.
- 就在那里。
你的新馅饼。
- Hm.
- Wait, no!
- 嗯。
- 等等，不！
You can't improve
the Krabby Patty.
你无法进步
蟹肉饼。
It's perfect perfection
that cannot be perfected upon.
这是完美的完美
这是无法完善的。
- Yeah, right.
Sensitive to time.
- 是的，对。
对时间敏感。
Make me 200 of these, pronto.
马上给我做 200 个。
Here you go, gentlemen.
Two brand new patties.
给你，先生们。
两个全新的肉饼。
both: Hmm.
两人：嗯。
Huh?
啊？
- Step right up and get
your new, improved patties.
- 站起来并得到
你的新改良的肉饼。
Ah! Uh.
啊!呃。
- I'm leaving a good review.
- 我要留下好评。
- So tasty.
- 太好吃了。
- Hm. A little bit different,
- 嗯。有点不同，
but they taste familiar.
但它们尝起来很熟悉。
Well, that wasn't familiar.
嗯，那是不熟悉的。
'Cause there's sesame seeds
growing out of your back.
因为里面有芝麻
从你的背上长出来。
* *
**
- Ohh.
- 哦。
Ehh, I never shoulda eaten four.
呃，我不应该吃四个。
Uh! Ah!
呃！啊!
Huh!
哈！
- The new patties!
They're making everyone change!
- 新的肉饼！
他们正在让每个人都改变！
- I gotta get out of here!
- 我得离开这里！
Ah! Oh! Oh! Oh! Ah!
啊!哦！哦！哦！啊!
- Maybe I'll pass on this patty.
- 也许我会把这个肉饼传下去。
Ohh!
哦！
Bite my buns.
咬我的馒头吧
Ooh!
哦！
- Eat us!
- Ahh!
- 吃掉我们！
- 啊！
both: Eat us!
两人：吃我们！
- Car 521, we have an outbreak
of rabid patties.
- 521车，我们爆发了疫情
疯狂的肉饼。
- Yeah, yeah.
I'm on my break.
- 是啊是啊。
我正在休息。
Go ahead! Come on,
I'm on my break!
前进！来吧，
我正在休息！
- Ahh, ahh, ahh.
- Eat us!
- 啊啊啊啊啊。
- 吃掉我们！
- Ehh.
- 呃。
Um--uh!
嗯——呃！
Ahh! Huh!
啊！哈！
- Eat me.
- 吃我吧
Is this some kind of
这是某种
new promotional gimmick?
新的促销噱头？
Surely, you can do better
than this, Eugene.
当然，你可以做得更好
比这个，尤金。
I mean, you even
wasted real pickles
我的意思是，你甚至
浪费真正的泡菜
on this cheap costume.
在这件廉价的服装上。
Pretty insulting, if you ask me.
如果你问我的话，这真是侮辱。
- Eat us.
- 吃我们。
- Ohh, whoa! Whoa, whoa!
- 哦，哇！哇哦！
- Ryan!
- 瑞安！
- Uhh, ah! Open wide.
- 呃，啊！敞开。
- No.
- Here comes the choo-choo.
- 不。
- 咕咕声来了。
- No! Uh--
- 不！呃——
Mm, mm, mmm!
嗯，嗯，嗯！
That's not so bad.
那还不错。
Ahh! Ahh! Ahh!
啊！啊！啊！
* *
**
All original Krabby Patty,
why did we forsake
全部原装蟹黄饼，
我们为什么放弃
your perfect recipe?
你的完美食谱？
Ohh.
哦。
- Chow down, SpongeBob!
- 吃点东西吧，海绵宝宝！
- Uh, no thanks.
- 呃，不用了，谢谢。
Already ate. See?
已经吃了。看？
Ohh!
哦！
Ah, uh.
啊，呃。
Maybe I'll be safe in here
till this all blows over.
也许我在这里会很安全
直到这一切都结束。
- This is Perch Perkins
reporting live
- 这是鲈鱼珀金斯
现场报道
from The Krusty Krab,
where I am one
来自蟹堡王，
我在哪里
of three people still unaffected
by this rabid patty pandemonium.
三人仍未受影响
被这狂热的帕蒂混乱所困扰。
The second unaffected person
is in this dumpster.
第二个未受影响的人
就在这个垃圾箱里。
Care to comment, sir,
on the chaos?
麻烦大佬评论一下
关于混乱？
- Pearch Perkins, how did you
know I was in here?
- 皮奇·帕金斯，你怎么样？
知道我在这里吗？
- I was napping in this dumpster
- 我在这个垃圾箱里打瞌睡
when you snuck in,
seeking refuge.
当你潜入的时候
寻求庇护。
- Take a bite!
- No! No!
- 咬一口！
- 不！不！
- Wait! Who's the third person
not affected?
- 等待！第三人是谁
不受影响？
- P-P-P-P-P--
Plankton!
浮游生物！
Ahh!
啊！
- Plankton. The Chum Bucket!
- 浮游生物。密友桶！
both: Eat us.
两人：吃掉我们。
Eat us.
吃我们。
- Ehh, ehh.
- 呃，呃。
- Ahh!
- 啊！
There it is, Karen.
就是这样，凯伦。
152 bags of grade B
pre-cooked chum
B级152袋
预煮密友
and not a single customer's
come through that door.
并且没有一个客户的
从那扇门进来。
How are the customers
supposed to get in now?
顾客怎么样
现在应该进去吗？
- Those aren't customers
out there, Plankton.
-那些不是顾客
在那里，浮游生物。
They're all Krabby Patty
zombie monsters!
他们都是蟹黄派蒂
僵尸怪物！
And they're forcing
everybody to eat them.
他们强迫
每个人都去吃它们。
You and I are
the last two survivors!
你和我是
最后两名幸存者！
Heh, I'll believe it
when I see it.
呵呵，我就信了
当我看到它时。
- Okay, I believe it!
- 好吧，我相信！
Karen!
凯伦！
- Consume me.
- 吞噬我。
- No!
- 不！
Hey!
嘿！
- Have some.
- No. Wait!
- 来点吧
- 不，等等！
I don't want--
我不想——
Have a slider.
有一个滑块。
Oh!
哦！
Stay back! I've got sporks!
退后！我有勺子！
Boy, do I feel better!
男孩，我感觉好点了吗！
- Oh, that's it!
Chum is the cure.
- 哦，就是这样！
密友是解药。
- Oh, a patty.
- 哦，一块肉饼。
Uh!
呃！
- Patrick!
- 帕特里克！
Feed us.
喂我们。
- No, eat chum. Wah!
- 不，吃密友。哇！
What happened?
发生了什么？
- Yes! Yes!
- 是的！是的！
- Ahh! Ohh!
- 啊！哦！
- Yah, uh, yah, uh,
yah, uh.
- 啊啊啊啊啊啊
是的，呃。
Maybe I should up the dosage.
也许我应该增加剂量。
Ahh!
啊！
And three, two--
还有三、二——
- Oh, my cranium.
- 哦，我的头盖骨。
- Ehh, I told myself
I'd never eat here.
- 呃，我告诉自己
我永远不会在这里吃饭。
- Oh boy, so much for
lab-grown patties.
- 噢，天哪，太多了
实验室种植的肉饼。
- You see, Mr. Krabs,
some things don't need
- 你看，蟹老板先生，
有些东西不需要
scientific reengineering
to be delicious.
科学再造
好吃。
The original Krabby Patty
is perfect just the way it is.
原来的蟹黄饼
就这样完美。
- Yeah, you know,
after all that,
- 是的，你知道，
毕竟，
a good, old vintage
Krabby Patty
一个好的、古老的年份
蟹肉饼
sounds pretty good right now.
- Yeah.
现在听起来不错。
- 是的。
Vintage Krabby Patties rule!
复古蟹肉饼统治！
- You're darn tootin', they do!
- 你真他妈的，他们就是这么做的！
And for the next three minutes,
all vintage Krabbie Patties
而在接下来的三分钟里，
所有复古甲米肉饼
in the Krusty Krab are...
在 Krusty Krab 中...
double the price!
价格翻倍！
- Wait! Don't leave now!
- 等待！现在不要离开！
Who's gonna clean up this mess?
谁来收拾这个烂摊子？
- Uhh!
- 呃！
Have some.
来点吧。